essayassist.com 2019-01-25

# Privacy Policy | EssayAssist.com

To successfully work with our Clients we require some personal information: telephone number, name and their country of residence. This information is used for various purposes:

  * Personal account ids created using this information. Knowing these details lets us better suit your needs and communicate in a more effective way.
  * To ensure that the order is on track we may need to communicate with our clients. It is imperative for the Company to contact the Client in case of any questions about the order arise.

**INFORMATION SECURITY**

We will never sell, share or rent to third parties any of personally identifiable data.

All the personal information we receive from Our Clients We store on our servers and do not share with any third parties. No information regarding the payment is shared. To protect our Clients’ security wee use sophisticated Secure Socket Layer (SSL) system. Only verified and reliable payment processors are used for financial affairs.

**COOKIES USAGE**

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on the Client’s hard drive, with their permission of course. These pieces allow the Company to receive some information about the Client’s activities on the website and valuable feedback to make our website and services even better.

Should this be an issue for the Client, The Company can stop monitoring the activities after the Client requests so. 

**DISCLOSING INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES**

All the personal information we receive from Our Clients is not shared with third parties under no circumstances. On some rare instances, we may share person al information with the expert who is working on the Order but only with explicit permission from the Client.

The Company retains the right to disclose non-personal information for marketing purposes.

**ONLINE CHILDREN PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE**

All Our services are offered under the COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act) standards, meaning the Client needs to be 13 years old and more to be able to order any of the services.

This Privacy Policy only covers the information gathered online.

We encourage the Clients to read the Terms and Conditions to make sure there will be no misunderstandings.

By placing an order, the Client accepts our Terms and Conditions.
